<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 <title>ABC</title>
 <link href="/tag/abc/index.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="/tag/ABC.html"/>
 <updated>2019-03-11T12:29:11+00:00</updated>
 <id>/tag/ABC.html</id>
 
 
 <entry>
   <title>Options for creating a new site with Jekyll</title>
   <link href="/options-for-creating-new-site-with-jekyll/"/>
   <updated>2018-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>/options-for-creating-new-site-with-jekyll</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll new &amp;lt;PATH&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; installs a new Jekyll site at the path specified (relative to current directory). In this case, Jekyll will be installed in a directory called &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;myblog&lt;/code&gt;. Here are some additional details:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To install the Jekyll site into the directory you’re currently in, run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll new&lt;/code&gt; . If the existing directory isn’t empty, you can pass the –force option with jekyll new . –force.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll new&lt;/code&gt; automatically initiates &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;bundle install&lt;/code&gt; to install the dependencies required. (If you don’t want Bundler to install the gems, use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll new myblog --skip-bundle&lt;/code&gt;.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;By default, the Jekyll site installed by &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll new&lt;/code&gt; uses a gem-based theme called Minima. With gem-based themes, some of the directories and files are stored in the theme-gem, hidden from your immediate view.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We recommend setting up Jekyll with a gem-based theme but if you want to start with a blank slate, use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll new myblog --blank&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To learn about other parameters you can include with &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll new&lt;/code&gt;, type &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll new --help&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Never stopped worrying or loving the bomb</title>
   <link href="/never-stopped-worrying-never-loved-bomb/"/>
   <updated>2018-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>/never-stopped-worrying-never-loved-bomb</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I’ve been through fire and water, I tell you! From my earliest pebblehood the wildest things you could imagine have been happening to this world of ours, and I have been right in the midst of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So begins Hallam Hawksworth’s The Strange Adventures of a Pebble. Written in the 1920s, the book was part of a series which also included The Adventures of a Grain of Dust and A Year in the Wonderland of Trees, all of which were supposed to introduce children to the world of Natural Sciences. In each of them, Hawksworth personifies the natural object he is exploring, and using a mixture of folk tales, scientific facts and colloquial, friendly explanations guides the reader through the history of the natural world. It’s a real thrill of a ride, dramatizing the life cycle of supposedly dull things. The Adventures of a Grain of Dust begins even more loudly than Pebble:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t want you to think that I’m boasting, but I do believe I’m one of the greatest travellers that ever was; and if anybody, living or dead, has ever gone through with more than I have I’d like to hear about it.
Hallam Hawksworth was the pen-name of teacher Francis Blake Atkinson. He was married to the author Eleanor Stackhouse Atkinson, author of the children’s classic Greyfriars Bobby, which was based on the (supposedly) true story of a Scottish dog who spent fourteen years guarding his masters grave. The couple were both committed to education and published a weekly magazine for Chicago high school students called The Little Chronicle, as well as working for Encyclopaedia companies later in life.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>External Featured Image</title>
   <link href="/is-intelligence-enough/"/>
   <updated>2018-01-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>/is-intelligence-enough</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Education must also train one for quick, resolute and effective thinking. To think incisively and to think for one’s self is very difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;We are prone to let our mental life become invaded by legions of half truths, prejudices, and propaganda. At this point, I often wonder whether or not education is fulfilling its purpose. A great majority of the so-called educated people do not think logically and scientifically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even the press, the classroom, the platform, and the pulpit in many instances do not give us objective and unbiased truths. To save man from the morass of propaganda, in my opinion, is one of the chief aims of education. Education must enable one to sift and weigh evidence, to discern the true from the false, the real from the unreal, and the facts from the fiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The function of education, therefore, is to teach one to think intensively and to think critically. But education which stops with efficiency may prove the greatest menace to society. The most dangerous criminal may be the man gifted with reason, but with no morals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The late Eugene Talmadge, in my opinion, possessed one of the better minds of Georgia, or even America. Moreover, he wore the Phi Beta Kappa key. By all measuring rods, Mr. Talmadge could think critically and intensively; yet he contends that I am an inferior being. Are those the types of men we call educated?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We must remember that intelligence is not enough. Intelligence plus character–that is the goal of true education. The complete education gives one not only power of concentration, but worthy objectives upon which to concentrate. The broad education will, therefore, transmit to one not only the accumulated knowledge of the race but also the accumulated experience of social living.&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
 </entry>
 
</feed>

